Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Board of Directors Files, 1942-1960; 1962-1988; 1970-1986; 1; 9.33 cubic ft.
  - Committee on Future Policy, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Institutions and Offender Services, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Conferences - Gangi, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1976; 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Constitution and Bylaws Committee, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Contribution Breakdowns, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correctional Association History, 1955-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correctional Association Legislative Mandate, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correctional Association Office, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correctional Association Staff, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correctional Association - Staff Media, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Attorneys, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (1 of 2), 1982; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (1 of 3), 1983; 3 folders (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (1 of 2), 1984; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED] (1 of 3), 1985; 3 folders (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Contains a letter from Jean Harris concerning drug addition rates among prisoners; Contains items housed in oversized material folder.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert, Outgoing, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert, Outgoing, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Board of Directors, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Dean, William, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Mushlin, Michael, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Powers, Susan, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - General, 1965-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - General, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - General, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - General, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - General, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Attica Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Fishkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Form Letter Responses [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Green Meadow Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Stormville Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Wallkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F. (President) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F. [RESTRICTED] (1 of 2), 1978; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F. [RESTRICTED] (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F., President, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F., President, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Media, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Media - Daily News, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Media - Newsday, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Media - Newsday, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Media - New York Times, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Media - Print, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Media - Television, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Media - Village Voice, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Membership, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - New York City Board of Correction, 1977-1978; 1982; 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - New York City Council, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - New York City Office of the Mayor, 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Contains signed letters from Mayor Edward Koch.
  - Correspondence - New York State Attorney General, 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - New York State Board of Parole, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - New York State Commission of Correction, 1978-1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - New York State Comptroller, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - New York State Department of Correctional Services, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - New York State Department of Criminal Justice, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature - Marino, Ralph, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - New York State Sentencing Guidelines Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - Pachoda, Dan (President), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Pachoda, Dan (President) - Pretrial Release Study, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - Requests for Information, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Congress, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Contains letters from Representatives Edward I. Koch, William F. Ryan, and Lester L. Woolf and Senators Birch Bayh and Jacob K. Javits.
  - Correspondence - US Department of Justice, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - Walker, George G. (Chairman), 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Walker, George G., 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - Wallkill Branch NAACP [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna (Board Secretary) [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - New York City Work Camps, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - White Street Jail, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice Policies, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice Policies, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dean, William T. (Chairman of the Board), 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Death Penalty Legislation - Testimony, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Endowment Restrictions, 1948-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Endowment Restrictions, 1948-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee - Guest Speakers, 1962-1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Federal Work Study Program (College), 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Finance Committee, 1961-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Finance Committee, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Finance Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Finance Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Financial Statements, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Financial Statements, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fourth Floor Certificate of Occupancy - Kenneth Ricci, Architect, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Friedlander, Shelley - Resume, Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Gangi, Robert - Appointment as Executive Director, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gangi, Robert - Speeches, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Kates, Erika, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lasker Reception, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Lasker Reception, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lasker Reception - Invitations, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Law Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Law Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Law Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Law Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Law Committee - Buchanan Case, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Proposals, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1969-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Liman Commission Correspondence, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Long Island Correctional Facility Closure - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - McKay Reception, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - McKay Reception, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - McKay Reception - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - McKay Reception - Invitations, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Media Contacts, 1980; 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Membership, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Membership and Media Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Membership and Media Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Membership Mailings, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership Mailings, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership Meetings, 1984-1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Membership Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Membership Statistics, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Membership Statistics, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., 1971-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Master Copies, 1968-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New York City Council, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New York State Budget Information Requests, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New York State Charities Registration, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New York State legislation - Governor's Proposed, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York State Recidivism, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1974-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Patterson Affair Follow-up, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Patterson Affair - Resources Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Patterson Affair - Working Lists, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Press/Broadcast Contacts, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Price of Punishment - Executive Summary, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Prison Construction - Press Release, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Prison Mental Health Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Prison Mental Health Committee - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Prison Visits - Brooklyn House of Detention Affidavits, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Prison Visits - Queens House of Detention, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Prison Visits - Queens House of Detention, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Prison Visits - The Tombs, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Program Committee, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Program Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Program Committee, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Program Proposals, 1973-1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Public Relations/Fundraising, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Public Statements, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Reception, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Reception, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Reception, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Reception Committee, ca. 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Reception Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Reception - Follow-up, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Reception - Mailing List, ca. 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Reception - Scroll, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Receptions, 1963-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Receptions, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Report on Financial Statements, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Reports and In - house Memoranda, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Requests for Information, 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Resources Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Resources Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party - Board Guest Lists, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Resources Committee - Cocktail Party Follow-up, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Resumes, 1962-2004 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Retreat, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Retreat, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Richards and Fenniman, Inc. - Insurance, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - RSVP - Volunteer Referral, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Samuels, Howard, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Scalare, A. Balfour, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Schwartz, Herman - Chairman, State Commission of Correction, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Search Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Contains copies of affidavits and court rulings concerning prisoners' efforts to unionize and the photocopied resume of future New Jersey governor Christine Todd Whitman.
  - Search Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Search Committee, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Search Committee, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Seth Sprague Educational and Charitable Foundation, 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Special Committee on Sentencing, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Special Committee on Sentencing, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Speech - Talking to My Brothers about Genocide, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Standing Committees, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Standing Committees - Osborne Association and CANY, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Statement - Marijuana Decriminalization, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Tax Exempt Status, 1961-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Testimony - Appointment Review of Chairman - State Commission of Correction, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Testimony - Capital Punishment, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Testimony - Juvenile Justice, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Testimony - Manhattan House of Detention, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Testimony - Minimum Standards, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Testimony - Minimum Standards, NYC Correctional Facilities, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Testimony - NYC Budget, 1984 May 11 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Testimony - NYC Jail Expansion, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Testimony - NYS Executive Advisory Committee on Sentencing, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Testimony - NYS Parole, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Testimony - NYS Proposed Executive Budget - FY 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Testimony - Selection of Judges, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Testimony - Senate Codes on Definite Sentencing, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Testimony - Tufo and Mayor on Investigations, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Testimony - White Street Jail, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Volunteers, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Weintraub, Judith F., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Annual Reports, 1844-1979; 2; 11 reels of 35 mm microfilm and bound copies
  This series consists exclusively of the annual reports on prison and jail conditions that the Prison Association/Correctional Association submitted to the New York State Assembly. The reports contain minutes of meetings, presidential addresses, committee reports, reports on individual prisons and prison conditions, prison reform campaigns in New York State, transcripts of testimony before the NYS legislature on pending policy measures, and lists of members and corresponding members of the Association. Reports published during the latter half of the nineteenth century chronicle the Association's role in establishing national and international prison reform organizations and conferences and furnish information about prison policies elsewhere in the United States and the world.
  Arranged chronologically. The microfilm versions are housed in the University Library Microfilm Collection, call number HV 8987 P684. Bound copies of the 1867-1878 and 1921-1969 Annual Reports are also available in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  The Annual Reports are available on microfilm in the University Library's Microfilm Collection, call number HV 8987 P684.
  Bound copies of the 1867-1878 and 1921-1969 Annual Reports are also available in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
  - 1st Annual Report, 1844 (Reel 1, Page 1-64)
  - 1st Annual Report appendix, First Report of the Female Department of the Prison Association of New York, 1844 (Reel 1, Page 1-27)
  - 2nd Annual Report, 1845 (Reel 1, Page 1-138)
  - 3rd Annual Report Part 1, 1846 (Reel 1, Page 1-111)
  - 3rd Annual Report Part 2 Report of the Prison Discipline Committee; Folded Plates, 1846 (Reel 1, Page 1-404)
  - 4th Annual Report 2nd Edition, 1847-1848 (Reel 1, Page 1-579)
  - 5th Annual Report; Page 364 is misnumbered and 464; Page 395-396 are mutilated; Page 397-398; and pp. 399-400 are stubs, 1849 (Reel 1, Page 1-408)
  - 6th Annual Report, 1850 (Reel 1, Page 1-126)
  - 7th Annual Report, 1851 (Reel 2, Page 1-56)
  - 8th Annual Report, 1852 (Reel 2, Page 1-72)
  - 9th Annual Report, 1853 (Reel 2, Page 1-168)
  - 10th Annual Report; Page 89 is misnumbered as Page 8, 1854 (Reel 2, Page 1-222)
  - 11th-12th Annual Report; Issue Combined, 1855-1856 (Reel 2, Page 1-115)
  - 13th-14th Annual Report; Issue Combined, 1857-1858 (Reel 2, Page 1-83)
  - 15th-16th Annual Report; Issue Combined; Tape Damage, 1858-1860 (Reel 2, Page 1-70)
  - 17th Annual Report, 1861 (Reel 2, Page 1-52)
  - 18th Annual Report, 1862 (Reel 2, Page 1-117)
  - 19th Annual Report, 1863 (Reel 2, Page 1-512)
  - 20th Annual Report, 1864 (Reel 2, Page 1-367)
  - 21st Annual Report; Tape Damage, 1865 (Reel 2, Page 1-232)
  - 22nd Annual Report, 1866 (Reel 2, Page 1-500)
  - 23rd Annual Report, 1867 (Reel 3, Page 1-303)
  - 24th Annual Report 14 unnumbered plates; 3 unnumbered folded plates., 1868 (Reel 3, Page i-xxiv, 1-672)
  - 25th Annual Report, 1869 (Reel 3, Page i-xxvi, 1-514)
  - 26th Annual Report, 1870 (Reel 3, Page i-xviii,1-168,i-vii,1-642)
  - 27th Annual Report, 1871 (Reel 4, Page 1-152)
  - 28th Annual Report 5 unnumbered plates, 1872 (Reel 4, Page i-xvi, 1-198)
  - 29th Annual Report, 1873 (Reel 4, Page 1-173)
  - 30th Annual Report 5 folded plates (all mutilated), 1874 (Reel 4, Page 1-192)
  - 31st Annual Report 4 folded plates (all mutilated), 1875 (Reel 4, Page i-xvi, 1-197)
  - 32nd Annual Report, 1876 (Reel 4, Page i-xvi, 1-184)
  - 33rd Annual Report, 1877 (Reel 4, Page i-xviii, 1-30)
  - 34th Annual Report, 1878 (Reel 4, Page i-xvi, 1-30)
  - 35th Annual Report, 1879 (Reel 4, Page i-xl, 1-26, 1-233)
  - 36th Annual Report, 1880 (Reel 4, Page 1-51)
  - 37th Annual Report, 1881 (Reel 4, Page 1-47)
  - 38th Annual Report, 1882 (Reel 4, Page 1-31)
  - 39th Annual Report, 1883 (Reel 4, Page 1-66)
  - 40th Annual Report, 1884 (Reel 4, Page 1-95)
  - 41st Annual Report, 1885 (Reel 4, Page 1-50)
  - 42nd Annual Report, 1886 (Reel 4, Page 1-46)
  - 43rd Annual Report, 1887 (Reel 5, Page 1-52)
  - 44th Annual Report, 1888 (Reel 5, Page 1-79)
  - 45th Annual Report, 1889 (Reel 5, Page 1-75)
  - 46th to 47th Annual Report, 1890-1891 (Reel 5, Page 1-136)
  - 48th Annual Report, 1892 (Reel 5, Page 1-72)
  - 49th Annual Report, 1893 (Reel 5, Page 1-223)
  - 50th Annual Report, 1894 (Reel 5, Page 1-215)
  - 51st Annual Report, 1895 (Reel 5, Page 1-1005)
  - 52nd Annual Report, 1896 (Reel 6, Page 1-133)
  - 53rd Annual Report, 1897 (Reel 6, Page 1-166)
  - 54th Annual Report, 1898 (Reel 6, Page 1-196)
  - 55th Annual Report Part 1, 1899 (Reel 6, Page 1-129)
  - 55th Annual Report Part 2, 1900 (Reel 6, Page 1-71)
  - 56th Annual Report, 1900 (Reel 6, Page 1-71)
  - 57th Annual Report; 8 unnumbered plates; 1 unnumbered folded plate, 1901 (Reel 6, Page 1-184)
  - 58th Annual Report; 8 unnumbered plates, 1902 (Reel 6, Page 1-156)
  - 59th Annual Report; 21 unnumbered plates, 1903 (Reel 6, Page 1-162)
  - 60th Annual Report; 26 unnumbered plates, 1904 (Reel 6, Page 1-163)
  - 61st Annual Report; 21 unumbered plates, 1905-1906 (Reel 6, Page 1-197)
  - 62nd Annual Report; 24 unnumbered plates, 1907 (Reel 6, Page 1-135)
  - 63rd Annual Report; 16 unnumbered plates, 1908 (Reel 6, Page 1-128)
  - 64th Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1909 (Reel 6, Page 1-133)
  - 65th Annual Report 27 unnumbered plates., 1910 (Reel 7, Page 1-119)
  - 66th Annual Report 29 unnumbered plates., 1910 (Reel 7, Page 1-110)
  - 67th Annual Report 46 unnumbered plates., 1911 (Reel 7, Page 1-228)
  - 68th Annual Report 42 unnumbered plates., 1912 (Reel 7, Page 1-288)
  - 69th Annual Report 38 unnumbered plates., 1913 (Reel 7, Page 1-516)
  - 70th Annual Report 30 unnumbered plates. 1 unumbered folded plate, 1914 (Reel 7, Page 1-583)
  - 71st Annual Report 27 unnumbered plates., 1915 (Reel 8, Page 1-494)
  - 72nd Annual Report 28 unnumbered plates., 1916 (Reel 8, Page 1-548)
  - 73rd Annual Report 2 unnumbered plates., 1917 (Reel 8, Page 1-198)
  - 74th Annual Report, 1918 (Reel 8, Page 1-110)
  - 75th Annual Report 10 unnumbered plates., 1919 (Reel 8, Page 1-121)
  - 76th Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1920 (Reel 8, Page 1-195)
  - 77th Annual Report, 1921 (Reel 8, Page 1-96)
  - 78th Annual Report 5 unnumbered plates., 1922 (Reel 8, Page 1-151)
  - 79th Annual Report 3 unnumbered plates., 1923 (Reel 8, Page 1-260)
  - 80th Annual Report 6 unnumbered plates., 1924 (Reel 8, Page 1-159)
  - 81st Annual Report, 1925 (Reel 9, Page 1-111)
  - 82nd Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1926 (Reel 9, Page 1-162)
  - 83rd Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1927 (Reel 9, Page 1-96)
  - 84th Annual Report, 1928 (Reel 9, Page 1-120)
  - 85th Annual Report, 1929 (Reel 9, Page 1-169)
  - 86th Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1930 (Reel 9, Page 1-159)
  - 87th Annual Report, 1931 (Reel 9, Page 1-137)
  - 88th Annual Report, 1932 (Reel 9, Page 1-124)
  - 89th Annual Report, 1933 (Reel 9, Page 1-149)
  - 90th Annual Report 1 tape damage, 1934 (Reel 9, Page 1-139)
  - 91st Annual Report, 1935 (Reel 9, Page 1-175)
  - 92nd Annual Report, 1936 (Reel 9, Page 1-104)
  - 93rd Annual Report, 1937 (Reel 9, Page 1-141)
  - 94th Annual Report 1 unnumbered plates., 1938 (Reel 9, Page 1-93)
  - 95th Annual Report 3 unnumbered plates., 1939 (Reel 9, Page 1-127)
  - 96th Annual Report 5 unnumbered plates., 1940 (Reel 9, Page 1-133)
  - 97th Annual Report 4 unnumbered plates., 1941 (Reel 10, Page 1-133)
  - 98th Annual Report 5 unnumbered plates., 1942 (Reel 10, Page 1-147)
  - 99th Annual Report 6 unnumbered plates., 1943 (Reel 10, Page 1-105)